# Shaniquo McKenzie

Toronto, Ontario, Canada

shaniquo-m@hotmail.com



1-437-225-0055



linkedin.com/in/shaniquo-mckenzie



https://shaniquo.github.io/

### **Summary**

It is my opinion that life is a journey which allows one to develop a unique set of skills that can be harnessed and transformed into one's niche. I welcome any opportunity that allows me to grow in experience and wisdom so I would in turn be able to help others gain these experiences through various means.

~ S. McKenzie.

Highlights of Qualifications

- · Active volunteer who always helps others and maintains a positive attitude
- · Member of Toastmasters International

### **Experience**

### SHN Epic Support Staff

Scarborough Health Network

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021 (4 months)

- Assisted hospital staff with the navigation of the EPIC environment
- Assisted with trouble shooting of hardware devices
- Reported and documented issues that need escalation to resolve

### Peer Academic Coach

Centennial College

Mar 2021 - Dec 2021 (10 months)

- Aided students in developing learning skills and time management strategies
- Taught techniques such ad POMODORO and SQ4R to aid student's in academic success
- Assisted students with study challenges and taking accountability issues

### Peer Tutor

Centennial College

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021 (2 years 1 month)

- Scheduled one on one meeting with students to solve course specific issues
- Created practice scenarios for students to understand specific topics in software engineering related courses such as programming (C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, Python, SQL etc.)

# Business Analyst

**CIBC** 

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 (5 months)

- Assisted with tasks set out by various teams, such as research, application testing & development etc.
- Worked closely with different team members to learn more about the company

- Completed required training courses and other work-related tasks as required

### Seasonal Customer Experience Associate/Cashier/Sales Floor Associate

Walmart Canada

Apr 2020 - Jul 2020 (4 months)

- Stocked and cleaned shelves
- Cashed items purchased by customers while marketing other items
- Greeted customers and assisted in finding the items they requested

## Software Lab Assistant

Centennial College

Dec 2019 - Apr 2020 (5 months)

- Maintained, installed, and configured software on computer systems
- Ensured computer, networking and telephony equipment are operational
- Monitored Open Lab sessions and worked on a software project using python and MSSQL



### Hospitality

Super 8

Feb 2019 - Apr 2020 (1 year 3 months)

- Ensured all rooms were cared for and inspected according to company standards
- Maintained a safe work environment and to replaced equipment as needed
- Dealt with reasonable complaints and requests with professionalism and patience

#### Education



### 🔤 Centennial College

Software Engineering, Health Informatics Technology 2019 - 2021



### The University of the West Indies, Mona

Bachelor of Science - BS, Animal Biology & Biotechnology 2012 - 2016

### **Licenses & Certifications**



SSSS SAS® Programming 1: Essentials - SAS

#### **Skills**

Customer Service • Software Development • Machine Learning • Data Analytics • Azure DevOps • Databases • Health Informatics • Technical Support • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Visio

#### **Honors & Awards**



🔤 Star Tutor - Centennial College

Apr 2021